(Scene:)- Leonard.
- What?
- My mom bought me those pants.
- I'm sorry.
You're gonna have to call her.
Sheldon, I am so sorry
I dragged you through this.
(Sheldon:)It's okay. It wasn't my first pantsing
and it won't be my last.
(Leonard:)And you were right about my motives.
(Leonard:)I was hoping to establish
a relationship with Penny...
...that might have someday led to sex.
SHELDON:
Well, you got me out of my pants.
(Leonard:)Anyway, I've learned my lesson.
She's out of my league, I'm done with her.
(Leonard:)I've got my work.
(Leonard:)One day I'll win the Nobel Prize
and then I'll die alone.
(Sheldon:)Don't think like that.
You're not going to die alone.
(Leonard:)Thank you, Sheldon.
You're a good friend.
SHELDON: And you're certainly
not gonna win a Nobel Prize.
This is one of my favorite places
to kick back after a quest.
(Howard:)They have a great house ale.
PENNY:
Wow, cool tiger.
Yeah, I've had him since Level 10.